letsmix.com 2011-05-26

# Privacy policy - Let's mix

Membership in Letsmix.com requires that Let's Mix AB records your name, address, date of birth (Civic Reg. No.), e-mail address, age, sex and telephone number. The purpose of this registration is primarily to prevent and facilitate the tracing of any non-approved activity. Your personal data will also be handled by us so that you will be able to use Letsmix.com and its functions in the best possible way, so that we can provide you with information and offers from us, from other Let's Mix companies or our cooperation partners, and for direct marketing via e-mail or other Letsmix.com functions.

The personal data which are stored in connection with marketing measures will be deleted within one year from the finalization of such marketing.

Let's Mix AB is the entity responsible for the processing of your personal data (sv Personuppgiftsansvarig), and you should contact us if you wish to correct any of the data or if you wish to receive information about our handling of your personal data.

Let's Mix AB safeguards your rights as an individual. Of course, we follow the legislation and regulations which exist – e,g, in the Personal Data Act – in order to protect you personal rights. Only a limited number of persons with special authorisation have access to the information about you.

Let's Mix AB will not sell any of your personal data, such as your address, telephone number or e-mail address to any third party.

It is your responsibility to ensure that correct data are submitted. This applies particularly to your age, since it is our intention never to send direct advertising to any person under the age of 16 years.

Once a year, you are entitled to request information from us free of charge relating to your personal data, and you can at any time withdraw your permission for our processing of your Civic Reg No. You also have the right to inform us in writing if you do not wish your data to be used for direct marketing. You can also request that data are removed or changed if they are found to be inaccurate or incomplete.

From time to time, we may make changes in our Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are, so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the Privacy Policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use Members' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify by posting a notice on Letsmix.com for 30 days.
